I'm going to get you.
Who is all you want is all you want is all you want is all you want is all you want.
Is all I see or see but a dream with energy.
I
Oh
But
I just had to dream past for all of my house.
I've always had dreams that I carried this girl.
I've always had dreams that I carried.
I have a dream that I have dreamt of,
and I was here with all of you.
Now my dreams come true.
I'm a real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real, real,
Cause to lose all my sadness that is just so too big for me, oh baby, good bye I did it again, I baby, you're all, you gotta love, cause I came, oh baby, baby, who's the cute thing coming up, that's it from above, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent,
I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent, I'm not that innocent,inin' be better like crazy, I don't have the word for you now but it's just so too much perquè esamián, I tell what I27s are and I 명かせみ's to choke about everyday things, but that's just so much bullshit as I feel take it back,
I'll take it again, I'll bring it to your heart
I'll ask you to keep on baby, baby
I'll ask you to keep coming love
And I'll send from my heart
I'll knock that in a cell
I'll take it again, I'll bring it to your heart
I'll ask you to keep on baby, baby
I'll ask you to keep coming love
And I'll send from my heart
I'll knock that in a cell
I'll take it again, I'll bring it to your heart
I'll ask you to keep on baby, baby
I'll knock that in a cell
Baby, I'm so into you
You got that something, what can I do?
Baby, you spin me around
The ear is moving, but I can't get around
Every time you look at me
My heart is jumping, it's easy to see
But then you mean so much more
More than anything I ever thought before
You got me crazy, I just can't sleep
I'm so excited, I'm in a two deep old regime
But it feels alright
When anything is the view keeps me up all night
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I'm so excited, I'm in to be crazy
But if it was alright, every time it's midnight
Stop!
You got me crazy, me crazy
I'm so excited, I'm in to be crazy
But if it was alright, every time it's midnight
Stop!
You got me crazy, me crazy
But if it was alright, every time it's midnight
Stop!
I'm so excited, I'm in to be crazy
Thank you!
How do you guys feelin'?
I want everybody to make noise for HBO!
Yes!
I want to welcome you to a world where anything...
I mean, it ain't fun!
The brink, brink, brink down
I'm so excited, I'm in to be crazy
What a day is my night, what a day is my night
It's bad, I'm so interested
It's all gone
I'm a detective, a nurse
okay, smile
I don't need nobody telling me just what I wanna
What I wanna wanna wanna wanna
I do about my destiny
I say no
Nobody telling me just what I wanna
I'm so bad over people telling me to be
Someone else, pardon me
I sure
Yeah, what about it new in my dad
What about it I don't wanna say
I'm with the first and the worst right
You've just got to do it
You're way I get it
I'm way I feel
But my life has been so long
I'm good-tested
I don't need nobody telling me just what I wanna
What I wanna wanna wanna
What I wanna wanna
Do about my destiny
I say no
Nobody telling me just what I wanna
I'm so bad over people telling me to be
Someone else, pardon me
What I wanna do to with my life
You don't wanna fight out no one's face
You just got to do it
You're way I get it
I'm way I feel
But my life has been so long
I'm good-tested
Once upon a time
In a quiet town on an empty street
There was a beautiful magic
Music box
And inside the music box
Live the girl
A girl
So innocent, so pretty
But so alone
And she would sit
Every day on her pedestal
Day and night
And she would dream
Of the moment when someone would find her
Someone with the key to the music box
And she would think
Someone
Who would watch me dance forever more
And maybe just maybe
That someone would be my true love
And he would find a way to free me
And show me the whole wide world
And maybe just maybe
We would live happily ever after
Yeah
Oh
Oh my
Oh yeah
Oh
I know that we could make it live
I don't know how to live without your love
I was fine to make you happy
Because you're the only one who can run
Always on forever you and me
That's the way our life should be
I don't know how to live without your love
I was fine to make you happy
Oh
I like it, I do it, it is coming now
I like it, I like it
I like it
I like it, I like it, I like it
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it
I like it, I like it
I like it, I like it, I like it
I like it
I like it, I like it
A dream will do just fine
So hold fast to your dreams, my darling
Never lose sight of your dreams
I like it
I'm not your body, I smoke today
But now I'm stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but a wave
I'm only missing feeling me no more
I am stronger than I ever thought that I said me
Like I, like I
I used to go
But now I'm stronger than I ever thought that I said me
Like I, like I
I used to go
With a pose
Did it just
Now it's nothing
You, why don't you feel that I can take it
That you know
That now I'm stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but a wave
I'm only missing feeling me no more
I am stronger than I ever thought that I said me
Come on now
Here I go, on my own
I am missing feeling me no more
I am stronger than I ever thought that I said me
Like I, like I used to go
With a pose
Did it just
Now it's nothing but a wave
I'm only missing feeling me no more
I am stronger than I ever thought that I said me
Like I, like I
I used to go
With a pose
Did it just
Now it's nothing
You, why don't you feel that I said me
Like I, like I used to go
With a pose
Did it just
Now it's nothing
You, why don't you feel that I said me
Like I, like I used to go
With a pose
Did it just
Now it's nothing but a wave
I'm only missing feeling me no more
I am stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but a wave
I'm only missing feeling me no more
I am stronger
I am stronger than yesterday
Are you feeling sweet?
And she loves me
But she loves me
She loves you
It is so good to be here tonight with all of you
I am gonna
Are you guys having fun so far?
Well, I'm gonna slow things down just I need to catch my breath
Before I get started I want to get something off my chest
Okay, first I want to say how proud I am of our nation right now
To come together how we have to these hard times it is really beautiful to watch
Seriously, and we have a very special treat for all of you tonight
We've set up a satellite feeds in four different locations so we can say hi to the troopers of America
First up we have the Lakeland Air Force base in San Antonio
Nice
They are so beautiful. Oh my gosh next we have the US Army Joint readiness training center and park folk Louisiana
Which is where I'm from
Next we have the US Marine Corps in Camp Pendleton California
And last but not least we have the flight maguina will air station in California
So
I just wanted to say that I know it's because of our the hall hard work
You do in the sacrifices you make that give me the freedom to do what I love to do which is
Perform for all these beautiful people
And I want everyone to give a round of applause so give it up for them again
Okay, I feel better now. I had to get that off my chest
I want to say
To you guys a song that's really special to me. It's
Really just about growing up and
What I'm going through in my life right now when I'm experiencing
But I'm yet to experience um
You know I know I get a lot of flag for what I wear and what I say and what I don't say
But I'm not a little girl anymore
And I guess I do those things because the way I feel inside and I also know
That I'm a young lady and I have a lot to learn and a lot to experience and I guess
What I'm trying to say is is that the way I feel right now inside I feel so wonderful because I'm doing exactly what I love to do
And I'm experiencing all of my wildest dreams and
My advice to you is to never ever lose your passion to dream
Please
Okay, I'm gonna stop
I'm gonna sing one of my songs. It's called not a girl
I used to think
I had the answers to everything
But now I know
Life doesn't always go my way
Yeah
Feels like I'm caught in the rainbow
Oh
I'm not a girl
Not
All I need is time
I'm on the planet's mind
While I'm in between
I'm not a girl
There is no need to protect me
It's time that I
Learn to face up to this
I've seen so much more than you know
So don't tell me to shut my eyes
I'm not a girl
Not yet a woman
All I need is time
I'm on the planet's mind
While I'm in between
I'm not a girl
But if you look at me close to me
There you will see in my eyes
This girl will always find
You
I'm not a girl
I'm not a girl don't tell me what to believe
Not yet a woman
I'm just trying to find the woman in me
All I need is time
I'm getting close to the planet's mind
While I'm in between
I'm not a girl
Not yet a woman
Oh
I need is time
A woman that is mine
While I'm in between
I'm not a girl
Not yet a woman
Stop it
Please
I'm not a girl
I really didn't realize how hard it was
To start a band
To do it
The doors
And the Beatles
We all have good hair
You know with the cowbell
Just don't do it this time
I'm not officially in the band yet
But I've been working on Master in the Cowbell
That was happy birthday
Stevie Wonder though
It's supposed to be a not a girl band
You know that's what I felt
But my brother
You know he has all the equipment
And the gear and stuff
I'm more than you Brian we can replace you
No you can
My name is Amina Abdul Chalil
I'm kind of the leader of our band
The only one with real talent
You know I play the bass
Since kindergarten
You know my mother taught me
And then she incorporated the whistle
So I play the whistle and the bass
Baby
Some people tell me I have a voice
That's a combination of where I am with me
My voice has become just a new talent I've discovered
It came about a month ago
I realized that God gave me this talent
To just be an amazing singer
Who let the dogs out
You guys
I think I got it watch this
Who let the dogs out
Who
Now that I don't know
When I was younger and we were
Playing musical chairs
You know I just felt the energy between us
And I knew
Don't you know any other chords besides G
Nancy?
My name is not Nancy
It's Alias
You get it
I think it's easy
You think this is easy right here?
You would
Get a close-up right here on my hands
This is art
We still have our artistic differences
You know we do
That's not the vibe of our music
Our music
Music
Makes the people
Come together
No, no, no, no, no, that will not work
No, so we've been working on a new song
Tell me what you think about this
Friday, Saturday, Sunday night
That's when I wash my hair
Oh, yes, she washes her hair
Oh, she washes, she washes
It's dirty
We really haven't figured out a name for the group yet
Why don't we write a song first?
Why didn't this just be my name?
Because you're not the only one in the group selfish
Don't be a child, Brian
Child, what about flower child?
What about dark child?
What about Destiny's Child?
No, that one over there
Go just smile, everyone just smile
No smiles, we should look intense
Is it a poser brand?
This is a grow group, just get out of the way
Get a wig
We should all be in black
You know rock and roll
You know rock and roll, right?
I love rock and roll
Roll, roll, roll
Do it
I'm trying to step by the rock at the shore
I knew he must feel about seven years
I feel this gun is strong
And playing my favorite song
Tell you what would be all
Tears with me, yeah, man
I can feel it would be long
So tears with me, yeah, man
I love rock and roll
You could've known a diamond with you by speed
And I love rock and roll
It's gonna take time and dance with me
I'm so sorry, I've gotta love this for a second
But that's a matter of sickle so sorry
You said you'd take your home
But we can't wait
And that's where we've been all
When years were made, yeah, man
We're moving on and singing the same song
Tell you what would be all
I love rock and roll
You could've known a diamond with you by speed
And I love rock and roll
It's gonna take time and dance with me
I'm so sorry, I've gotta love this for a second
I love rock and roll
It's gonna take time and dance with me
I'm so sorry, I've gotta love
And that's where we've been all
When years were made, yeah, man
We're moving on and singing the same song
Tell you what would be all
I love rock and roll
So put another diamond with you by speed
And I love rock and roll
It's gonna take time and dance with me
I'm so sorry, I've gotta love this for a second
But that's a matter of sickle so sorry
You said you'd take your home
I love rock and roll
It's gonna take time and dance with me
I'm so sorry, I've gotta love this for a second
But that's a matter of sickle so sorry
You said you'd take your home
I love rock and roll
It's gonna take time, dance with me
I'm so sorry, I've gotta love
And that's where we've been all
I love rock and roll
We're moving on and singing together
I really enjoy Fine
to be
about
I'm gonna have to go back to the
place where I was supposed to go.
I'm gonna have to go back to the place where I was supposed to go.
Don't oblivion risks anything to corporations.
Don't يا a lawyer find a better driver than劊The Betray
Did you do what you was wishin' ?
What...?
Why apps are me, why feet are meible, probably me !
I'm not gonna do that you want to take home
Wanna make me know
You've been over my life
Just what I did before
But I'm a fool
You took the time to realize
I'm not the cause of sacrifice
You've been over my life
So if you wanna feel my pain
You'll leave it
So modulate my shoes
To me right or I'm through
Can't you see that if you lose my road
You got some bigger be out
For a ticket time when you lose
This is my game
My rules
And I can't see
I'll be asleep
Baby you don't know what it's like to feel me
But you get interested
For a while
You took the time to get my heart to win
You've been over my life
Just give you a baby
I'm not the other is me
Baby I need some more
To realize
I'm not the cause of sacrifice
You've been over my life
So if you wanna feel my pain
You'll leave it
So modulate my shoes
To me right or I'm through
Can't you see that if you lose
This is my game
My rules
And I can't see
I'll be asleep
Baby you don't know what it's like to feel me
But you get interested
For a while
You took the time to get my heart to win
You'll give you everything
I'll go去
Don't you wanna feel my pain
Love me
Can't you see that if you lose
This is my game
Don't know who's there
Walk them on my shoes
This is my game baby
I know I am playing sugar
I'm telling you
You got the pick of me
Tell me
I'm gonna be
And I'll be asleep
Baby, you're done
But it's right to be me
This is telling
You just got to sit down
Huh?
Don't know
Who I am
I'm just
Because I recognize
I'm really ready for it
And I yeah yeah
I think of all the times that I've been said
I think of all the times that I've looked you bad
Ain't no way of being lonely
I don't wanna let you back in
Let's just be safe
I'm up alone and I want to back
The thoughts that I will be lonely
I don't wanna let you back in
Ooh
So may how to feel
Maybe that you're right
Once made up from cool
And I just got no more off here
And as good as we need no more
So may the best
And you can do better
Now I look for me
And I just like to be
And I think
Take cause I'm really ready for it
I'm really ready for it
And I yeah yeah
I think of all the times that I've been said
I think of all the times that I've looked you bad
Ain't no way of being lonely
I don't wanna let you back in
Let's just be safe
I'm up alone and I want to back
The thoughts that I will be lonely
I don't wanna let you back in
Ain't no way of being lonely
Ain't no way of being
Maybe that you're right
And you're so much better
And I'm tired of trying to leave behind this
What's better to do
Yeah
Come on
I'm a bitch, I'm a bitch
Think of all the times that I'll be sad
Think of all the times that I'll talk to you about
Ain't no way of being lonely
I don't wanna hurt you back in
Let's just be sad
I don't wanna know, never want you back
Just drop that out, we'll be lonely
I don't wanna hurt you, think of all the times that I'll be sad
Think of all the times that I'll talk to you about
Ain't no way of being lonely
I don't wanna hurt you back in
Let's just be sad
Drop that out, we'll be lonely
I don't wanna hurt you back in
This is all you mind
Don't forget your man's education
And that's pro, she don't come
Congratulations all your way from Vita
Next up is that you leave from Vita
Put that in, down
I'm out of the line
Give it up for Vita
She comes to you all the way from Alaska
To the left and the right and the left
Up to the other, for Vita
All we got for today is a house
All the way from Sector's
And that's pro, we're lonely
We got all the way from Sector's
Give it up for Vita
This is a match all the way from New York
This is Kiana from Chicago
Hello
Hey, I'm Yolanda Goatsonai
Yeah!
Alright!
You're ready?
Woo!
No!
Let's do this tonight!
I'll be the葉岸!
It's like this, the葉岸!
I'll go brotherоз,
We're good,
No fear, we're good,
We're good tonight,
Woo!
I'm gonna save you, right?
Ooh!
All right everybody, I want you to do me a favor online.
She does words on the other screen.
I want you to see this song with me, okay?
You do it?
Woo!
Oh, no, you can't.
I'm gonna trust you.
Are you ready?
One, two, one, two, three.
I'm gonna do it.
Two, three, I'm gonna be in tears of pain.
This is our song, we play a game.
I want nobody with you.
We'll be in this way.
Let's do this tonight.
I'm being in tears of pain.
This is our song, we play a game.
I want nobody with you.
You're feeling this way.
Let's do this tonight.
I'm being in tears of pain.
This is our song, we play a game.
I want nobody with you.
We'll be in this way.
Let's do this tonight.
I'm impressed.
You guys are really good right here.
Yes, I was feeling it.
Woo!
Oh my goodness.
It's a little hot in here, right?
I'm gonna ask you a question.
Have you ever heard a song that just kind of like took over your body or something?
You don't know, you kind of felt like a slave to the music.
I know maybe I'm like that.
I've got feelings too.
And I need to do what I feel like doing.
So let me go and just listen.
I'm gonna go and make a move right.
Make a move right.
Oh yeah.
I'm gonna deny it, I'm not your name.
Baby, don't you wanna dance up on me?
That's a spoon of the tonic, please.
Oh baby, don't you wanna dance up on me?
I think I called my name and name.
Let's jump.
Make a move.
Woo!
You want me to
Baby, don't you wanna
Because I said for me
I said to you
So I love the time and then
Only pair
Don't you wanna
Dance up on me
You're ready
You're my mama name and age
This lady
I'm your like right now
I can't not hold me
So I wanna
When I first leave
I'm gonna be like
I'm not just
You're like
Being child
Just being child
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't
5 of travers party top 10 song!
I wanna thank all of you guys for playing with my girlfriend, ladies.
Thank you.
Let's give it up for H.P.O.F.L.
Give it up for my dancers, so that's the end of the world.
Woo!
Woo! Thank you guys for having a good night!
Let's give it up for H.P.O.F.L.
Woo!
It's time to be brave, brave, come tonight!
I must confess that my loneliness is killing me now!
So, you won't ask me a word, you'll be here, and give me a sign!
Give me a baby one more time!
Woo!
I won't be this baby's killing me now!
I must confess that I still believe!
I must come up with you, I lose my mind, give me a sign!
Give me a baby one more time!
I won't be this baby, you're killing me now!
I must confess that I still believe!
I'm not this baby, you're losing my mind, give me a sign!
Give me a baby one more time!
I must confess that I still believe!
It was just a dream!
Dream of energy!
It was all my mind!